(Sun Honglei)
(Li Naiwen)
(Guo Jingfei)
(Liu Yuning)
(Gong Jun)
(Chen Xingxu)
(Wang Yuwen)
(Lin Yi)
=Wow The World S2=
(New Zealand, Queenstown)
(Today is the final day
of the New Zealand trip.)
(As the Extreme Sports Capital,)
(Queenstown)
(is the birthplace
of commercial bungee jumping.)
(So today, the Earth Group)
(will experience)
(the Kawarau Bridge Bungee)
(and the Nevis Swing.)
(Let this thrilling leap)
(put an exclamation mark
on this New Zealand trip.)
=Episode 5 (Part 1)=
(Brave Souls Enjoy the World First)
Someone's coming.
(Next door: Li Naiwen, Guo Jingfei,
Chen Xingxu, Lin Yi, Guesthouse)
Who's coming to my place?
(The neighbors are visiting again)
Every day, we trek over mountains
to visit them.
After dark, they cross hills...
After dark, they cross hills
to come find us.
Morning.
Good morning.
Morning, bro.
How are you feeling, bro?
Hey, handsome.
How are you feeling?
I'm okay. How did you sleep?
I was definitely asleep by then.
Not a single minute wasted.
Are you mentally prepared?
Handsome guy.
I'm fine.
(Bungee jumping)
My take on bungee jumping is that
whoever makes me jump,
[*"Jump" pronounced as "Beng" in Chinese]
I'll get mad at them.
[*"Mad" pronounced as "Ji" in Chinese]
Bungee ticks you off.
[*"Bungee" pronounced as "Beng Ji" in Chinese]
Let's go.
(What is Nai looking for?)
Nai, we should head out.
(Phone Hide and Seek)
Where's my phone?
Can't find your phone?
(Xingxu has a way)
I'll show you a trick.
Press this button.
(3 meters)
Over there.
You find it right away.
I didn't know this function existed.
- I taught you, right?
- That's amazing.
Right, remember it next time, okay?
Got it.
You look like an eggplant.
I'll treat you to eggplant.
He'll dislike you today.
I think.
(Refusing the eggplant)
How come you've lost weight
after filming for so many days?
Me?
We haven't treated you well enough.
We should have prepared
an all-eggplant feast for you.
Thanks.
We should set up a competition.
The loser...
The loser has to eat eggplant.
Would you like to play?
I'm not playing.
Not even for a second.
I absolutely can't lose.
I'll book a flight straight home.
Be careful.
Lin Yi, don't hit it.
Let it go.
Move away from it.
Just walk away.
Go.
Don't hit it.
Because your hair color
is much like a flower.
(Too beautiful)
A bit fragrant.
I'm pretty looking forward
to today's activity.
Why did Honglei dare to jump yesterday?
You were dead set
against jumping at first.
(Sun Honglei)
When I got there,
that valley
was like
a mother's embrace.
I felt like if I didn't jump...
I really wanted to jump down.
Yesterday, I just suddenly felt like
I could do it.
Nai thought he was up
for skydiving yesterday,
but after waking up today,
he changed his mind...
I still can't do it.
Nothing I can do.
After the adrenaline wears off...
Yeah.
Yesterday, I was really excited,
you know?
- Don't feel what you felt yesterday anymore.
- Right after the paragliding yesterday,
I wanted to hop on a plane immediately.
Do it again.
Go skydiving.
- He really wanted to do it again.
- Yeah.
He said, "Let's do it again."
He also wanted to experience
the hang glider
yesterday.
The hang gliding was so fun.
Don't talk about it. We missed it.
(Arriving at
the Kawarau Bridge Bungee site)
Come on.
Let's go on an adventure.
Adventure trip, second stop.
Oh, my!
Will they ride bikes and leap down?
(Professional extreme sports performance.
Do not attempt to imitate)
♪Otherwise, just forget it♪
(Getting cold feet)
♪Maybe let's just forget it♪
Welcome to
the first stop on the final day
of Heartbeat Journey.
The bridge in front of us
is the Kawarau Bridge,
built in 1880.
It was originally a vital transportation route
during the gold rush era.
But in 1988,
two crazy young people
strapped an elastic cord to their ankles
and leaped off the 43-meter-high bridge.
They transformed the traditional
vine jumping custom
of Pacific Island peoples
into a modern adventure sport,
making this spot home to
the world's
first commercial bungee jumping site.
This is the birthplace of modern
commercial bungee jumping?
The birthplace.
A bungee jump here is well worth it.
That's really meaningful.
Because of this bridge, Queenstown
has become a sacred destination
for bungee jumping
and gradually grown into
the Extreme Sports Capital of the World.
But Li Naiwen has a new
take on bungee jumping.
He said, "Whoever makes him jump,
he'll get mad at them."
(No problem)
So bungee ticks him off.
Let's head indoors first
and kick off today's
bungee journey with a mini mission.
Today, we'll play a little game
called Brave Yes Man.
One of the eight of you
is the Yes Man.
Today, he can only
say "Yes" to everything.
Today, we'll carry on with
a four-on-four team battle.
The winning team
gets to assign the Yes Man
to either side.
Whichever team the Yes Man is on
has to send every member bungee jumping.
(The whole Yes Man team
is going bungee jumping)
How do we decide who the Yes Man is?
About how we decide who is the Yes Man,
(Guo Jingfei)
earlier, we asked everyone to
write down how eager you are
to try bridge bungee jumping.
(Write down your willingness level
to go bungee jumping)
(Li Naiwen: 0)
(Liu Yuning: 0.01)
(0.01 more courage than you)
(Sun Honglei: 2)
(Guo Jingfei: 3; Wang Yuwen: 89.8)
(Zhou Ye: 30; Chen Xingxu: 100)
We'll make the decision based on
your willingness scores.
(Chen Xingxu)
The one with the highest score
will be today's Yes Man.
That's good.
So Lin Yi
is today's
(Lin Yi)
Yes Man.
(Yes Man: Lin Yi,
Willingness Score: Infinite)
Infinite.
Yeah.
Infinite?
Jump anytime, no problem.
I've never tried bungee jumping before.
Doing my first jump here,
the birthplace of the world's first
modern commercial bungee site,
feels incredible meaningful.
Come on. Let's have
the Yes Man decide the teams.
Okay, you make the call.
(Wang Yuwen)
I'll choose the three
with the lowest scores.
(0.01 points, 2 points, 0 points)
The four of us.
Trust me.
My game quotient is extremely high.
All the smart brains are on this team.
Then we're sure to win, right?
We're sure to win.
Yeah.
All smart people.
None of the four of us
is afraid of bungee jumping.
Looks like the person
on your left is scared.
Me?
How would I know?
You're dressed like a pilot today.
Let's all be polite today, okay?
Okay.
(Suddenly obedient)
Let's not attack each other, okay?
Flight jacket today.
Today, our first mission
is called 7-Second Heartbeat Charades.
Split into two teams of four
for a 4v4 battle.
(Li Naiwen)
Three teammates take turns describing
while one person is responsible
for guessing the answer.
(Liu Yuning)
The describers use gestures and actions
to let the guesser figure out the word.
(Zhou Ye)
Each describer gets 7 seconds per round.
Same number of questions,
the one with less time spent wins.
If your team wins,
you can send the Yes Man
to the opposing team.
(The winning team can decide the Yes Man's fate)
That team will be the ones bungee jumping.
For example,
swimming.
For instance, you can say,
"Two hands, slide alternately."
You watch him do this gesture.
Then you say, "In the water."
Then you'll know it's swimming.
Mainly, these three people...
These three have to keep
the clue-giving granularity consistent.
Yeah.
(It's a battle of unspoken rapport)
With Lin Yi here, they can't win.
Why?
His thinking
(Loud gossiping)
won't be confined
within the scope of these given prompts.
Lin Yi, indeed.
You really misunderstand me.
(Just wait and see)
Who guesses?
Xingxu.
Yeah.
(Me?)
The three of us are better at
describing things.
What do you mean?
(Loves to tease Xingxu)
Your physical strength is better.
What do you mean?
To avoid getting Yes Man
sent over to us,
we need to try our best to win.
We definitely have to work hard.
(Going all in!)
Must work hard.
Fei.
Have you ever fought for your life
in a game?
Never.
But today
is my home turf.
Going all out.
Don't lose too quickly.
Which team goes first?
We'll go first.
(Confidently going into battle)
Come on.
The other team sends one person
to hold the pole.
(Control pole)
Come on. I'll hold it.
The controller can randomly
point to one person to describe.
I'll do some work.
(Super proactive)
Xingxu.
With our tacit teamwork
and expression skills,
- don't humiliate them too badly when we win.
- No problem.
Okay?
- Leave it to me.
- Okay.
We must keep Yes Man far away.
We must win.
Alright.
We must win today.
Just to let you know that
fate is so unfair.
But I have to say.
We don't want the Yes Man
transferred to our team,
not because we're scared
of bungee jumping.
We just hate being forced into it.
We want the freedom to choose
whether we jump or not.
(Mastering our own destiny)
So we're keeping him off our side.
A glamorous queen is a glamorous queen.
(Leading lady demeanor)
Actually, it's still because
Fei decided to go all out today.
(Bring it on)
(Competition begins)
Come on.
I suddenly feel a bit nervous.
(Inexplicable panic)
You also get nervous?
Relax.
Show us your brilliant smarts
from the other day.
You can do it, bro.
In this universe, I am the smartest.
It's easy. Come on.
(Prompt: Malatang)
Point randomly, right?
Yeah.
(Start describing;
Headphone music pauses)
(Malatang)
Make an okay gesture.
Then hold it in front of your mouth.
(Trying to describe eating)
Blow a whistle.
No.
Okay.
(Time's up for describing;
Next person takes over)
Make a peace sign
and put it by your mouth.
(Chopsticks in place)
Then your right hand...
(Time's up)
Curve the fingers up. Place them before your lips.
Is it whistling?
(Next one)
Make a peace sign with your hand.
Then cup your other hand.
Cup it.
Then that peace...
(Serious)
(Jingfei continues)
What does it mean?
(Who are you asking?)
(Is it two characters?)
(They told me to do this gesture)
Three characters.
(You did the gesture wrong)
(Then what?)
Three, two, one.
(Time's up! Next one)
(This is a competition)
Wake up.
It's over?
(Apologetic smile)
(Tell me something I don't know)
Three characters.
Do you skip the remaining seconds?
(What did you say?)
(With an opponent like this,
it's a sure win)
Okay, it's your turn.
(The glamorous queen steps in)
Make a peace sign. Put it sideways by your mouth.
Then jump up.
Keep jumping.
Okay, turn around.
Move the peace sign down.
Circle past your other hand
and raise it higher.
The peace sign is like a pinch.
Pinch.
Pinch?
(Chen Xingxu, Y2K pose appreciation,
Aesthetic accumulation, Armpit pose)
(Summoning the brain master)
Pinch.
(Get this pose?)
(Beyond my understanding)
If it's like this,
this round is over.
(Didn't I pinch it well?)
Always talking nonsense.
Grasshopper's Club Broken Heart.
Put the peace sign by your mouth.
Then start jumping.
Then fan with the other hand.
(So hot)
- Fan? What does that mean?
- Pucker your lips.
Wipe sweat.
Then pant.
What does that have to do with hands?
(Synchronized recreation)
(This time, it will definitely work)
Make a peace sign with your lips.
Make...
(What on earth are you saying?)
Make a peace sign with your lips.
(Is there a risk I might
actually pull it off?)
Make... Make a peace sign
with your hand.
Nip the front tip of the peace sign
gently with your mouth.
(Forced to mute)
(A particularly clingy Beijing man)
Stretch your hand forward quickly.
Then pull it back fast.
Pull it back fast.
- Tap forward and retract instantly.
- Alright.
Open and close
your peace sign repeatedly.
Keep moving from your left hand
to your mouth.
No.
What is this?
What does it mean?
I don't know either.
Do you know what this word means?
I know that word.
Okay, time's up.
Time's up.
(Chats about everything
except serious matters)
Chatting away.
Stick out your tongue.
Then fan your tongue with that hand.
(Fanning tongue?)
(A bit salty)
That hand.
Fan your own tongue.
Too hot to taste.
Eating hot pot.
(You try again)
Hot.
Yes.
The third one.
The third character is correct.
There are only
three characters in total.
Spicy...
(Finally)
Spicy Pot.
You got the third character right.
The third character is correct.
Malatang.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
I suggest you switch players.
I'll go guess.
You go guess.
Tell them
you're way better than them.
Teach them how to play.
Okay?
Stop flattering to trap me.
You try it.
You'll know how desperate Fei is.
(See through it)
He just wants to get through these seven seconds.
Yeah.
Come on, start.
(Awesome, Love to watch)
(Fei, prove yourself)
(Pluck the wool)
For this thing...
The first character....
No.
The first character is... Pass.
What? Any useful clues?
Never in my life have I found talking
so tough.
Three characters.
Stretch your arms open
and reach forward.
Kneel down.
Then...
Okay.
(Thank you for your participation)
The second character is...
Lift your head up.
A pun.
- Lower your head.
- Sheep.
(Looking up, Sheep)
[*They sound similar in Chinese]
Yes.
You say...
Tell me what you got.
You say it first.
Sheep.
(Sheep what?)
(Cat, Spear)
[*They sound similar in Chinese]
Sheep what?
Time's up.
We won.
Open your palm fully.
Then tug it out forcefully.
Pull.
Change another one
and you'll get it right.
Pluck.
Pluck the wool.
Yes.
Fei always keeps everything to himself.
(Complaint)
He just said,
"Actually, I know this word."
Why are you always chatting?
Do you just want to...
No, because my mouth is really...
I'm terrible with words.
You can't turn back and just say,
"This is too simple."
- "Actually, you could have guessed it."
- Sorry.
Why are you talking nonsense?
Glamorous queen.
Calm down.
Give it your all out for this round.
Okay.
Okay?
Show the sense of duty as an adult.
Okay, time to grow up
and stitch my childish pants shut.
You're like a fisherman.
You're having so much fun.
Okay. You play it and I guess.
Okay.
Come on.
(Prompt: Curling)
Kneel on one knee.
Half-clench your hand into a loose fist.
Then place it on the ground.
Look at your hand.
Then push it out.
(Nailed it)
(So standard)
Bowling.
Now,
stand up, hold an object
and rub it back and forth.
Rub it back and forth.
(Only three seconds)
Dice.
Go back to the movement
you did just now.
Touch the ground with your hand.
Then start shaking.
Yes.
Dice.
(That's right)
I'll mainly describe
the second character.
Make a fist with your right hand,
and rest it under your chin.
Rest it under your chin.
Make a hollow fist and comb downward.
Comb downwards.
Comb.
- Yes.
- Beard.
Facial hair.
[*Pronounced as "Hu Xv" in Chinese]
The first character.
What pot?
[*"Pot" pronounced as "Hu" in Chinese]
Urinal.
[*Pronounced as "Niao Hu" in Chinese]
Chamber pot.
[*Pronounced as "Ye Hu" in Chinese]
Lie down, lick the ground
and your tongue gets glued.
Curling.
[*Pronounced as "Bing Hu" in Chinese]
Their descriptions were excellent.
Just push it forward.
Yes.
- This is already amazing.
- Yes.
My movements were also very standard.
But
I didn't guess it.
(What are you so proud of?)
Come on.
(Prompt: Latin dance)
Three characters.
The last character,
stretch your hand out.
Stretch out one hand with palm open.
Then stand your hand up steady.
Stand upright.
(How to explain "stand"?)
- Okay. - Stand.
(What is "stand"?)
Three characters.
I'll describe the first character first.
Make a six with both hands.
Touch your pinky fingers together.
Don't put them on your head.
Okay.
Okay, come on.
Your middle finger and your thumb,
stick them together.
Middle finger and thumb...
Do you understand?
Yes.
Peacock.
Do that pose toward me.
Stand your hand up.
One hand.
Spread your fingers.
Then face me.
(Eyes blazing like torches)
Palm facing me.
Yes, what is this thing?
This is the last character.
Five.
[*Sounds like "dance" in Chinese]
- Yes.
- Five.
Tiptoe your right foot.
Hike your hips.
Shift front and right.
Cha-cha.
Samba.
Ballroom dance.
The first character. Squat down.
(Squatted down)
Squat down.
Strain.
(Those who understood laughed)
(Guys, is this right?)
Strain.
Then wipe with something.
Pull.
[*Pronounced as "La" in Chinese]
Okay.
Pull.
Five.
Latin dance.
Come on.
You can do it.
You're already
a genius at playing this game.
You are the king.
(Prompt: Come and catch me)
Come on, three, two, one, go.
Run by alternating your feet.
- Run by alternating your feet.
- Yes.
Turn around and run backwards.
Run while glancing back.
Then laugh.
Stretch your right hand out
to embrace forward.
Embrace forward?
Laugh out loud.
Stretch out your right hand and beckon.
Come and catch me.
Nice.
Okay.
I'm so impressive.
(Terrible describing,
Top-tier deciphering ability)
Dear audience, did you see that?
(The audience offstage cheers for you)
Can you guess it?
So fast.
In such a flash.
(I'm back on top)
(Last prompt: Skyrocket)
Squat down.
(Squatted down again?)
Make a lighter with your hand.
Light it.
(Laughs)
My stomach hurts a lot.
What?
(Laughing until my stomach hurts)
My stomach hurts a lot.
- Pinch your nose.
- Okay, time's up.
(What's going on?)
Use one of your hands
to make a thumbs-up gesture.
Then move your thumb up and down.
(Just did that)
Yes, cover your ear with the other hand.
Three characters.
Then look at the sky.
This thing goes up into the sky.
Double-bang firecracker.
Time's up.
Set off firecrackers.
Left hand on your head.
Left hand where?
(Really can't take it)
On your head!
Right hand on your skull.
Left hand on your head,
right hand on your skull.
Right hand on my head.
Head and skull are two different things?
Head and skull are two different parts.
Stand up and do a horse stance.
Then scratch your armpits
with both hands.
Then jump.
Monkey.
Open both hands.
(Can't hold it in at all)
Opened.
(Out of sight, out of mind)
Left hand on your head.
Right hand on your face.
Then bend your right hand a little.
Squat down and light the fire.
Monkey.
Squat.
(Not judging, just describing)
Squat down and light the fire.
Then look at the sky.
Go back to my move.
Go back to my...
They're messing with you, Jingfei.
Jump up instantly on your right foot.
Go back to my previous move.
Then say "hehe".
Then tilt your head.
Yes, three characters.
You can't even guess this?
A lifetime of good reputation.
Go back to what I said before.
The action of scratching your armpits.
Is there a character for monkey?
[*"Monkey" pronounced as "Hou" in Chinese]
Of course.
Of course, there is.
Even the audiences have all guessed it.
Yet you still haven't.
Skyrocket.
[*Pronounced as "Cuan Tian Hou" in Chinese]
(Time taken: 10 minutes and 30 seconds)
This...
Isn't this obvious?
It's even like this. Isn't it obvious?
It's monkey, I know.
But I've been thinking.
You said stomachache.
The stomachache is the "cuan" part.
[*"Cuan" means "diarrhea" in Chinese]
Cuan.
I was wondering
what does stomachache mean.
Held the stomach for so long,
saying stomachache.
I even made him squat
and pinch his nose at the same time.
That's so vivid.
When I saw them playing,
I completely forgot
about bungee jumping.
- I'm not even nervous anymore, really.
- Chatting with them, unconsciously...
(Finish the bungee jumping)
It's okay.
Come on. Give me the pole.
I'm alive again.
Come on. Let's do this.
Yuning, you go first.
I'll guess first then.
Okay.
(Started working out)
I feel like I can't be worse than they.
It seems like when watching,
you think you understand it perfectly.
But when you play yourself,
you're clueless.
(A hint of worry)
Go!
(Prompt: Secret; Timer starts)
Hold your hands up.
Walk forward.
Yes.
(Determined gaze)
Three characters.
The first character.
Stick out your index finger.
Okay.
Then the...
(Time's up)
(You do it)
Lin Yi's turn.
Yes.
Then your left hand
scoops downwards.
Yes.
Clockwish.
[*Slip of the tongue]
No, clockwise.
(Sarcastic remark)
Isn't this very easy? Really.
Left hand back and forth.
Yes, back and forth.
Back and forth, up and down,
back and forth.
(Up, down, front, back)
Yes.
(Up, down, back, forth)
Down.
Up.
Up, down, up, forward...
Down, forward, up, back.
Down...
What is this?
Down, forward, up, back?
Yes, your right hand
is the first character.
One.
The last character
is the first action I just showed you.
Yes.
This is the third character.
Lift?
You know the first character now, right?
One.
Think about it yourself
based on the first character.
(Anticipating)
You can figure it out.
You two are good friends, aren't you?
(Another me in the world)
No useful information.
(This is...)
No, still the same move as before.
Yes.
Then pull it out.
The last one, a big pull.
Then open your hands and laugh loudly.
(Well done, bro)
(What is this?)
What is this?
You know the first character now, right?
One.
[*Pronounced as "Yi" in Chinese]
This is the third character.
(Carrying something)
[*"Carry" pronounced as "Duan" in Chinese]
Clean sweep.
[*Pronounced as "Yi Guo Duan" in Chinese]
(Correct answer: Clean sweep)
Lin Yi, come.
(Wait, bro)
Nai.
Haven't guessed it yet?
(It's obvious)
This is still...
Arms crossed over chest.
Stand.
Look at the ground.
Then
nod while moving to the right.
give a smug laugh.
(Do you feel the same, Yuning?)
Palm.
Hold it up.
Fingertips pointing at me.
Change direction,
fingertips pointing at me.
(How can I do it?)
Thumb pointing up.
One palm.
(Time to go back)
Then move up and down.
Up and down.
One hand.
(Ignoring the referee?)
Go back!
Yuning.
No.
- We all guessed it.
- Guessed it.
Impossible.
- Really.
Hold up your left index finger.
Then pulls that with the right hand.
Pull with the right hand.
Just this move. Yes.
Pull to the last one,
and then open both hands and laugh.
And then
arms crossed over chest.
Nod and then laugh loudly.
(Such a long plot)
Three characters?
String them together.
Okay, finished pulling.
(Relieved)
(Praising regardless)
So cool.
Really, you're so cool.
Although you can't guess it,
you're very cool.
(Being cool is enough)
(Try again)
Do you remember the move
I just mentioned?
That quick one.
That palm.
Just one hand.
Then...
What are you holding?
Mixed stew.
[*Pronounced as "Yi Guo Hui" in Chinese]
Clean sweep.
This is too hard.
The "Guo" is too hard to describe.
[*"Guo" can refer to "pan" in Chinese]
"Guo" is hard to describe.
Then what do you mean by this?
What is this?
You are
the justice officer.
And then you are like this.
What does a justice officer
have to do with clean sweep?
There are a bunch of criminals
squatting in the front.
(Trying to understand)
Criminals.
(Suddenly enlightened)
Okay, fine.
I get it.
Okay, I understand.
(As long as you understand)
No, you just didn't get into his role.
His brain wiring is
completely off the charts.
Be serious, friends.
Be serious.
(Getting serious now)
Okay.
(Question: Walk the dog)
Extend your right hand.
Make a fist.
Thumb out.
Pinky out.
Shake.
Make a phone call.
Come on.
How many characters?
Two characters. Kneel on the ground.
Hands
placed on the ground.
Both hands placed on the ground.
Stick out tongue.
This is the second character.
Dog.
Walk the dog.
What does this have to do with it?
Six.
[*"Six" and "walk" sound similar in Chinese]
(Xingxu and Lin Yi share the brain)
Prop up.
Yes.
Walk forward.
Walk, yes.
That's it.
Two characters.
Dog crawl.
Walk the dog.
Quick.
I get it.
Too easy.
What does this mean?
Wonderful?
(Great)
Wonderful.
I guessed it based on this.
His "six" gesture.
I'm gradually receiving your frequency.
Received.
Okay.
Again.
This is simple.
(Already have a clear picture)
(Prompt: Domineering CEO)
How many characters?
Four characters.
Stick out your thumb.
Point at your nose.
(The domineering CEO himself)
(Indeed, it's me)
Put your palms together.
Then rub up and down.
Then cross your hands.
Both hands...
Fingers interlocked.
Yes.
This looks like Lin Yi.
The fourth character.
Make a peace sign.
Two.
Then open and close.
Cut.
One leg straight.
One leg bent.
No, not like this.
What is this?
No.
What does one straight
and one bent mean?
Bent.
Both are straight.
Just don't be the same.
Wait a moment.
Go back to my move.
Both hands' fingers interlocked,
and placed in front of chest.
And then
face swaying left and right.
Then tongue pushing against the cheek.
Tongue pushing against the cheek?
I know this one.
But what is it?
What is this?
Haven't guessed it yet?
(Signal lost)
What is it?
Haven't guessed it yet.
You... Yes!
Lin Yi is so cute.
What are you doing?
(I don't know either)
Still the last character.
Make a peace sign.
Yes.
Cut.
[*Sounds the same as the last Chinese character for CEO]
Yes.
Go back to my move.
He really "disdains" others' move.
Well, only push your tongue twice.
Just push once on each side.
And your head should have a rhythm.
Then when moving left and right,
do it faster on the left side.
Then syncopate, and then slow down.
Then go fast, syncopate, and slow down.
A glance back with a smile.
The first character,
stick out your thumb.
Then stick out your index finger.
Yes.
What is this?
A gun?
Eight?
[*Sounds similar to the first Chinese character for domineering]
This is a homophone.
Haven't guessed it yet.
Now step back.
Then put your hands in your pockets.
Both hands in pockets.
Then walk forward.
Walk.
Then,
suddenly
a syncopation.
(Syncopation again?)
Right hand suddenly extends
straight forward.
(Smooth)
Still flexing.
So cool.
No, right hand extends straight forward.
Right hand extends straight forward.
Eyes glance to the right briefly.
Then nod.
Nod three times, and then come back.
Eyes back.
Then do my combo moves.
Combo moves, wait.
(Domineering CEO syncopated return,
falling in love with me)
So cool.
Very accurate.
No, missing a person.
Act with him, and stand here.
(Partner on stage)
(This is a wall)
Yes, just this feeling.
Then rub hands.
Domineering...
(Have you guessed it, Yuning?)
Domineering CEO.
Do you still think it's simple, Yuning?
It's killing me.
But Lin Yi did it very accurately.
Lin Yi's description was very accurate.
But I thought it was a person's name.
I thought of a bunch of actors.
Don't dare to say.
Let me guess.
You do it.
(Question: Juicer)
Stick out your index finger.
Point forward.
Then,
stab.
(Prick)
Next stage.
(Next stage)
(Leave it to the next person)
Okay.
Three characters.
The last character
is the neck stretching forward,
and then retracting back.
Stretch forward, and retract back.
Chicken.
The last character.
Okay.
Grab something
with your hand.
Forcefully.
Squeeze.
Press.
Almost there.
Chicken.
Squeeze.
Squeeze chicken?
(Sudden illness)
(Oh, my)
(I myself?)
Here's the thing.
The first character.
Eyelids quickly close.
Blinking chicken.
Yes.
Then the second character.
Bow.
Suddenly stand up.
Suddenly stand at attention.
Yes, sudden military training.
Okay, bend.
Bow.
Stand.
Yes.
(What does this military training mean?)
Yeah.
What blinking chicken?
[*Blinking chicken and juicer sound alike]
Juicer.
(Completely clueless)
Awesome.
This one is very difficult.
Squeezing juice.
Keep squeezing.
Yes.
I thought I was guessing that character.
(Guessed it?)
Yes.
Succeed.
One more.
How many have they gotten right now?
Only four?
A long way to go.
We need to get 50 questions right.
Let's go bungee jumping.
Come on.
(Question: Lin Daiyu)
Extend a fist.
Hollow.
Empty fist.
Yes.
This is a number.
Number, zero.
[*The Chinese character for zero sounds similar to Lin]
Zero, zero what?
(Impressive)
Three characters.
Then put your palms together.
Then the top palm opens.
What kind of plant is this?
Flower.
Related to this.
(Getting better)
(Quick answer)
Peony.
No.
(Continues quick answer)
Big peony.
(Can you listen first?)
This...
(Not listening)
Big peony?
(Time's up, next)
Action word.
Verb.
Okay. Now,
scratch ears and cheeks.
Scratch ears and cheeks.
Then lift one leg.
Then suddenly point forward.
Then open mouth.
Yes.
What would you want to say?
(Confidently turning around)
(Losing the train of thought)
Squat down.
Jump forward.
Rabbit.
Almost there. It's an animal.
Jump forward while punching.
Yes.
What is this?
Both feet kick forward.
Kangaroo.
Second character.
First character.
Dai.
[*The first Chinese character for kangaroo]
Ling dai...
(Almost there)
Ling dai
ma?
(Ling dai ma?)
(Never heard of it)
Ling dai?
(Ling dai?)
(Ling dai ma, Ling dai gou)
(Lin dai biao, Lin dai shu)
(Ling dai shuai, Ling dai zi)
(Frantically forming words)
Flower.
Related to this.
Lin Daiyu.
Ling dai ma...
Lin Yi, your move
of scratching ears and cheeks,
what does it mean?
Scratch ears and cheeks.
Then lift one leg.
Lift one leg.
Then suddenly point forward.
Open mouth wide.
What sound effect
should be added at this moment?
Dai.
[*Sound effect for Monkey King]
(Shocking)
(Stunned)
Dai.
Your description...
This...
Even if you beat me to death,
I can't guess.
Come on.
You guess.
(Leaves the field with regret)
(Question: Feed goat milk)
Squat down.
Then bend over.
One hand, palm facing up.
Place it near the abdomen.
Then the other hand
stretches out straight.
Make that money gesture.
Then step back.
Muttering words.
(Confidence remains)
Beggar?
(Lin Yi's original intention)
Come on.
What are you doing?
Okay.
Both hands make a "six" gesture.
Place on head.
Then,
lower head and go forward.
Push forward.
What is this?
What animal is this?
Alpaca?
What is it?
Goat.
This is the second character.
First character.
Put down one hand.
Then place it near your ear.
Put that one near your mouth.
Pinky placed near your mouth.
Speak.
Say the first character.
(Hello)
[*Sounds similar to feed in Chinese]
Goad.
What are you doing?
Say which character?
Quick.
(The old couple
left in tacit understanding)
Still lift this hand first.
Place it near your ear.
What's the first sentence?
What's the first character?
How are you?
(That's very polite)
What do you say before that?
Hello.
[*Sounds similar to feed in Chinese]
That's it.
And then?
And then...
Hello, Brother sheep.
(The old couple never gives up)
The first two characters are correct.
Third character.
Put your fingers
on your chest.
What is that?
What is this?
Feed goat milk
(Time taken: 15 minutes 40 seconds)
Feed goat milk.
Okay.
Fei's team won.
(Guo Jingfei's team time:
10 minutes and 30 seconds)
(Lin Yi's group time:
15 minutes and 40 seconds)
Yes Man.
Sorry, my friends.
You did very well.
One step away.
So you can discuss now
whether to change people.
If you don't change people,
then the "Yes Man" group
needs to go bungee jumping.
Do you want to jump?
What's your attitude?
We are very arrogant.
(Sweating a little)
We're humble. We don't want to jump.
Help.
Do you want to fly a bit,
Fei?
No, I don't.
You're quite "flight-proof".
(Guo Jingfei)
[*Jingfei means flight-proof]
Ask Lin Yi.
Lin Yi, what do you want?
Who do you want to jump with you?
Xingxu.
How about you swap with Fei?
Or Xingxu swaps with Honglei?
Then your team jumps.
Then what about Naiwen?
Look at this watch.
(Heart rate spike warning)
No.
Lin Yi swap with Fei, okay?
(Saving Nai)
Just Lin Yi swaps with Fei.
How about this, Ye?
Later,
if you don't dare to jump...
I actually...
I'm just struggling.
Struggling, think a bit more, it's okay.
If you don't want to jump later,
I will jump for you.
It's okay. Don't be anxious.
It's okay.
If you're scared,
just tell me directly, okay?
I'll go jump.
Quickly tell him.
Just say you're scared.
Just say you're scared to him.
Bro, I'm scared.
I'll jump then.
That's just how I am.
That's the kind of man I am.
Truly a domineering CEO.
(Domineering CEO limited-time return)
Please accompany us.
But you probably can't bear to, right?
(Domineering CEO's speaking skills)
Okay.
Alright, that's it. Lin Yi, come over.
Okay, come.
Okay.
Lin Yi, come over.
(Bungee jumping members: Chen Xingxu)
(Wang Yuwen, Lin Yi, Zhou Ye)
Come on.
Okay, great.
Okay.
Okay, safe now.
We are the Cowardly Team.
I really want to try it.
(But then again)
I follow the rules.
Otherwise, the game would
be played for nothing.
Forget it, I won't jump.
Buddies, should we beat him up?
I can't take it anymore.
(Lei's concern)
How is it,
Wen?
Are you nervous?
My heart is beating fast now.
But I can't tell
if it's nervousness or excitement.
Have a Yili Yoghurt Chewy Lemon
to relax.
(Chewing)
How is it?
(Peel, pulp)
Lots of peel and pulp.
As I chew and chew,
(The more you chew, the more relaxed)
it seems I'm not nervous anymore.
You chew, it works.
I chew, it works.
(So enjoyable)
(It will definitely work)
It will definitely work.
You can do it.
Next,
let's go change equipment.
Hello.
(Weighing)
Do you mind filling this in, please?
(Matching rope safety parameters)
Yeah, okay.
Okay.
Directly writing your weight
on your hand.
What's this?
Your photos and videos.
My photo? Okay.
Super ceremonial.
Perfect.
(Putting on safety equipment)
Okay.
(Lin Yi's safety equipment
is fully worn)
(Chen Xingxu's safety equipment
(Zhou Ye's safety equipment
is fully worn)
Excitement outweighs nervousness.
Really.
I'm very excited now.
Wen, do you want to be the first one?
I'm fine either way.
(Wang Yuwen's safety equipment
is fully worn)
I'll jump first.
(I won't hold back)
Okay, you go first.
(Not yet psychologically prepared)
Come on, Buddy. Follow me.
I first?
You first.
No.
He goes first.
(Loves to joke)
You go first.
No, one.
Why? Who say that?
(Scared the child too much)
(Everyone's safety equipment
is fully worn)
(Preparing for bungee jumping)
Who goes first?
(Bungee jumping viewing area)
The scenery here is really beautiful.
(View from bungee viewing area)
I'll jump first.
Okay.
Yuning,
come on.
You can do it!
This platform is shaking.
We're shaking here too.
(Yuning is comforting)
Well, the senior group is all here.
Why is there a young person here?
I'm middle-aged,
middle-young, young-middle now.
Are they jumping from there?
Right there, they're there.
(Preparing for bungee jump)
Xingxu.
What's wrong?
Nervous?
I'm okay.
High five.
Great.
Awesome.
Why is your hand wet?
(Setting me up here)
Why is your hand...
I have a very brave image.
Don't
(Refusing OOC)
break it, okay?
Let me touch again.
It's okay.
Very dry.
Just fanned it a bit.
Ready to go?
(Relaxed)
(Solemn look)
The four of us are so cowardly here.
Too cowardly.
We're too ashamed to look,
I think.
But we admit it.
(Supporting courage freedom)
(Hold tightly)
Tsk.
Why are you shaking?
I don't know.
Just thinking about it
makes you feel scared, right?
(Already immersed)
They've never bungee jumped before,
and
it's the place
where modern commercial bungee jumping
was invented.
It's really meaningful, I think.
You sound like
you're reading from a script.
Actually, I really want to...
What do you want to say?
(What do you want to do?)
Just that feeling in the heart,
throbbing, excited.
I can go back and brag to people.
(Already reminiscing)
Yes.
I'd say,
"Last time when we went to New Zealand,
the place where modern commercial
bungee jumping was invented,
the bridge is super awesome.
I did my first bungee jump there.
I just gave it a try."
(Sounds very tempting)
Look, this can be a life experience.
(Jingfei also has something to say)
What I tell people would be
that I was at the world's first...
At such a meaningful place,
I held back.
Didn't jump.
Didn't go jump.
(Humorous)
This is a person's self-discipline.
(Redefining self-discipline)
So many awesome...
Such a famous landmarks,
yet I held back.
(A little rhyme)
Yeah.
I'm even more awesome.
A person's self-discipline.
Yes, indeed.
Who jumps first?
Should be Xingxu.
- Have fun.
- Enjoy.
(Chen Xingxu ascends
the bungee jumping platform)
(Can't hide excitement)
Wow!
(Still relaxed)
Wow.
(Scared)
Xingxu.
Xingxu, you can do it!
(Scared themselves but fully supportive)
Cool!
Xingxu, you can do it.
You can do it.
(Safely filmed under official guidance)
Are you ready?
Yes.
Just a moment.
(Bridge deck height from river surface:
43 meters)
I can't even watch.
Buddies...
I love you all.
(I love you all)
(So cheesy)
Bravo!
Wow.
(Relaxed)
I love you guys.
Wow The World.
The whole world is right here.
(Love you all)
Cool.
(Leap with courage)
(Rush towards the wind and freedom)
Xingxu.
Cool.
Love you.
Awesome.
Li Naiwen, you scratched me.
You know?
My muscle...
You ground a small piece.
(Hard to hold back)
Zhou Ye's mouth has never closed.
Close your mouth.
(Already scared silly)
Good, I caught it.
Okay.
Thank you.
I'm good.
It's my first time.
Okay.
It's here.
Thank you.
Very good.
Thank you, sir.
Bye.
I just want to do it,
without any hesitation.
But I was still scared.
If I were really...
Really...
If I was standing there,
extremely scared,
I was afraid the people behind me
might get nervous.
So I was hoping
to boost their courage a bit.
So cool.
Your face is swollen.
Yes.
It's because too much blood
rushed to it.
Did it feel great?
It felt amazing.
Amazing.
It felt amazing, not at all...
It was...
It was like this.
The moment of greatest pressure
was the instant right before you jump.
Yeah.
(Listening attentively)
Once you go down,
there's no sensation of weightlessness,
only a feeling of blood rushing.
Next one.
Zhou Ye.
(Preparing for bungee jumping)
You can do it!
It's okay, Ye.
It's totally fine.
Trust me.
How are you feeling?
My heart is beating so fast right now,
Guys.
My heart is racing.
Can I really do this?
Yes, you can.
Why wouldn't you be able to?
You can do ballet,
so what's stopping you from this?
(Warmly helping to ease her mood)
Your singing is already this good.
I admit you're the lead vocalist.
He already admits
you're the lead vocalist,
Ye.
I think so too.
(Ye thinks it's right)
You also think so.
It seems you're not
that scared after all.
You're the best.
Your turn?
Okay, let's do it.
Okay.
(Attempting the challenge)
You can do it. Ye, you're the best.
Brave Ye, unafraid of difficulties.
Standing here feels really different.
You can do it!
You are Xiaomahua.
What is Xiaomahua?
That role she played,
a very brave character.
No, it's so scary.
We're going to take a photo first,
then you go.
Okay?
It's like your toes
just hanging off the edge.
Okay, I want to say something.
You say something,
and I count you down, okay?
You can do it!
Your singing skills are better
than mine.
It's so hard.
It's okay.
It's really terrifying.
This is so embarrassing.
Don't look down.
Don't do it then.
She's crying. She's scared.
It's okay, crying is
a normal physiological reaction.
She's already great.
Okay, go.
Bravo!
Awesome!
You're my boss.
Brave Ye,
unafraid of difficulties.
(A small body not afraid to leap)
(Great courage holds up
the sky and earth)
I did it.
Nice.
That was amazing!
So cool!
Totally awesome.
All right.
That was amazing!
That was incredible.
She actually jumped.
Hello.
Help me, please.
All right.
Li Naiwen,
stop pinching me so hard.
He kept pinching me.
(Another one affected by Naiwen's fear)
That was amazing!
Thank you.
We'll bring you down.
Just stay there.
Very nice.
How was it?
Really good?
Yeah.
Is it your first time?
Yeah, first time.
Well done.
Zhou Ye.
Great.
Thrilling,
it was actually quite thrilling.
Once you jump down,
you'd feel
that hesitating
while standing there was really
terrifying.
It's better to just jump.
Bungee jumping,
it's nothing special.
(A small bungee jump, conquered)
I've conquered it.
So impressive.
Ye, you're amazing.
(Deeply admiring myself)
You're such an amazing Ye.
Whose turn is it?
Next is Wen.
Awesome, Yuwen.
Help me think of a slogan.
I haven't thought of one yet.
Just say, "Tell my mom
I'm no coward."
Tell my mom
I'm no coward.
I'm so excited.
(Completely unafraid)
This feeling of a racing heart.
(Jumping)
(The habit of being scared for others)
Don't jump, girl.
Okay, I won't pinch you anymore.
Let me pinch you.
(Another one affected by Naiwen)
Don't pinch me.
Why pinch me?
No, I'm afraid...
(Pointing out a better way)
Pinch the wood. There's wood here.
You can do it!
(Better pinch you)
Listen up, you guys over there.
This message is for you.
Okay.
I can't hear you.
The brave ones
enjoy the world first.
So cool.
(The brave ones enjoy the world first)
(Not just words)
So thrilling.
She didn't hesitate at all.
You two really are childhood friends?
Xingxu,
you two.
You two are childhood friends.
Well,
we were classmates
in the affiliated high school.
Classmates.
Which affiliated high school?
The Affiliated School
of the Dance Academy.
Bungee jumping
Feng Zhu...
(Bungee jumping affiliated)
Affiliated...
(Scared to the point of babbling)
Affiliated high school.
Okay.
That's awesome.
So cool, right?
I did it.
Yuwen is really impressive.
Okay.
So thrilling.
Oh, my. Why is it so thrilling?
Sometimes,
overthinking
will interrupt your steps.
So,
those who truly want to set out
won't talk much,
nor will they overthink.
Just do it.
My heart wasn't racing just now,
but this aerobic walk
made it speed up a little.
Actually, it wasn't scary.
After you jump,
you don't feel anything.
Right.
The scariest moment is only...
The instant you make the decision.
Great job.
Impressive.
Yuwen, you're amazing.
I really wasn't nervous.
You're so amazing.
So amazing.
Let me see your face.
Just a little.
Just a little bloodshot.
It's okay.
You cried, bro?
I didn't.
It's not that bad.
He wants to jump so badly he cried.
But I really wasn't nervous.
It's Lin Yi's turn.
(0 frame to ignite)
Come on.
Coming.
Lin Yi.
You can do it!
In this moment, your singing
is better than mine.
Cool.
Lin Yi, you can do it!
Stand in the light.
Don't just stand there.
Be fierce!
(The youth advances fearlessly)
(Meet the passionate in the high sky)
Wow!
(Cracked voice)
♪The world is so interesting♪
Wow.
Once he came up, he'd be...
How was it?
Did I jump well just now?
Absolutely.
The voice is back.
Thank you very much.
Wow.
Thrilling.
But I wanted to sing a song.
I just sang half a line
and realized that in that state,
I couldn't make a sound at all.
(That's a pity)
I said, "The world is so..."
Then I couldn't continue.
Lin Yi.
Great job!
Thanks, Honglei.
But honestly,
before jumping,
looking at them
made me much more confident,
much more at ease.
I just felt like
they were accompanying me.
Luckily, there was this
viewing platform parallel to me,
allowing me to see them.
Otherwise, I might have also
stood there,
hesitating for a while, afraid to jump.
(Courage doubled by sharing)
(The partners behind turn solitary courage
into shoulder-to-shoulder)
So cool.
Yi.
Amazing.
- Yi.
- So cool.
What did you shout?
Be fierce.
So cool.
Yi.
Honglei.
Great.
We're all great.
All great.
Awesome.
In those three seconds
when I fell just now,
it was like my own Hitchcock shot.
(Hitchcock zoom lens)
A dolly zoom.
Because your eyes
will automatically focus.
Everything is flying backwards.
You know?
Whoosh, and you're in.
So that's what it's like.
Now I can better understand
their feelings.
It felt like time was compressed
for a moment.
Just like when we watch
those time-traveling shots.
With the visual radiating effect
on both sides.
Okay.
Everyone has experienced bungee jumping.
Next,
we will head
to one of the world's
largest canyon swings,
the Nevis Swing.
Okay.
Bro,
I'm back.
(Admiringly)
Xingxu, you're my idol.
You jumped down without any hesitation.
I'm totally impressed.
(Teasing you)
Bro, you even dared to bungee jump without a rope before.
Your constitution must be great.
My daughter's foundation
is the truly good one.
With Royal Friso's triple essence,
boosted by 3D protection,
external defense, internal protection,
and stable care,
it safeguards
the baby's strong constitution.
(Guarding all the way)
Nothing is impossible in growing up.
(Worthy of being called Uncle Nai)
No wonder you're called Uncle Nai.
Even the milk powder is so well-chosen.
Great job.
Let's go.
(Riding to the Nevis Swing)
So cool.
A big truck.
Nainai.
Watch me jump.
(Seemingly emotionally stable, but actually)
♪The uncles from my family♪
This bus is quite bus-like.
(Hearing your words
is like hearing words)
Since you haven't seen
what that swing really looks like...
Right.
Now, for the big swing,
those who think they can do it,
please raise your hand.
Did Zhou Ye raise her hand? Zhou Ye.
Zhou Ye is tired.
Zhou Ye can only go wild once.
(Burned out)
I raised my hand just because
I want my mom to see on TV
that I'm not a coward.
I can explain to her later
why I didn't go up.
I'll say I had diarrhea or...
There are many, many reasons.
Having diarrhea?
Sort of.
Done.
Already done.
Our T-Rex duo is kind of awesome.
Seems like we can do anything.
Kind of awesome.
As long as it doesn't require brains,
we can do it.
(Accurate self-assessment)
We excel at getting punished.
We just specialize
in getting punishment.
Right.
Any punishment is fine.
Direct punishment.
No process needed.
It must be a cliff,
because if it's not...
it will hit.
It can't let go.
101 now.
(Still scared)
Yuwen, tell him a bit more,
and it will reach 110.
It's a bit high.
I know the cliff is on the left.
(Bumpy)
This is already very scary.
It's too narrow.
It's right on the edge.
Scary.
There's smoke on both sides.
Can he see?
Is there a road here?
We can already see the mountain top
from here.
Such a mountain road.
Can't look right anymore.
It's right there, see it?
This side.
I see it.
It's here, Naiwen.
Li Naiwen.
You're everywhere.
He's already frozen.
In the middle. In that...
We'll be in that little box.
Ah.
That little box.
We'll be in the little box.
(HELLO!)
That's it. It's not bad.
Let's experience it.
We're here.
We must try this.
This...
Right, Nai?
I...
You can
do it, I think.
It's fine.
That's it?
That's it for today?
All that gym time
is just to strengthen your mouth?
What?
That's it?
The biggest tough talker in the world,
Liu Yuning.
At the door,
he's like, "That's it?"
I really have to try this.
(Almost tempted)
(Low-key)
Calm down.
Okay.
Basic operation. No big deal.
Don't be surprised.
No need to be too surprised.
You can ask your dad to buy you a GTR.
Do you think
there are extreme sports pros
who just hold on
and swing without any ropes?
Imagine those free solo climbers.
That's true.
Free solo climbing is really terrifying.
I downloaded a climbing game
the other day,
and that scared me pretty bad.
Well,
I was controlling the role.
I was controlling them all the time.
When they were falling,
I was screaming in front of the laptop.
Why are all the shoes hanging up there?
(What does it mean?)
What are these shoes for?
They were picked up.
These are all from the bungee jump:
the shoe that stayed on
when the other one fell off.
The people are all fine?
The people are fine.
(A little shocked)
We are currently
at the Nevis Swing.
(Nevis Swing: one of the world's largest. 160m-high platform,
300m pendulum, up to 120 km/h across the canyon)
The free-fall height is 70 meters
(Swing arc ≥300 meters)
with a swing arc over 300 meters.
When the participant falls,
they will trace a huge arc,
sweeping across the canyon
at a speed over 100 kilometers per hour.
Unlike bungee jumping,
the charm of the canyon swing
lies in the fact that it's not
a pure weightlessness experience
but a journey with an arc.
After the fear,
you will experience
a huge emotional release.
After the fall,
what you feel
is the sensation of flying.
This is the common feeling
everyone shares.
Sounds pretty fun.
We'll see in a bit.
Pretty fun.
Say something, Naiwen.
What's wrong?
Naiwen, wake up.
Naiwen,
speak.
He's dazed.
78 shoes are hanging above this.
Who can go on the big swing?
There's a very small task.
(Who Goes on the Swing?)
Each team sends a member
(Teams take turns asking "Who goes on the swing?" or "Who skips the swing??" Winners skip the swing)
to have one-on-one competition.
They take turns asking,
"Who goes on the swing?"
or "Who skips the swing?"
Whoever answers wrong
or can't keep up the rhythm
is eliminated.
The winning team gets the chance
to swap out Yes Man.
Best two out of three.
The team with the brave Yes Man
- will all challenge the canyon swing.
- Right.
We'll send Xingxu.
(Xingxu goes to battle)
You do it.
Come on.
(Choosing Liu Yuning)
Okay, come on.
Go.
You can definitely win.
Okay, come on.
Come on.
Xingxu.
(Round 1)
Who goes on the swing?
You go on the swing.
Who skips the swing?
I skip the swing.
Who goes on the swing?
You go on the swing.
(Rhythm error)
Okay.
Yuning, you're out.
Xingxu.
Great.
Couldn't keep up the rhythm.
(I'll do it)
Come on.
Game...
Game King.
Come on. Go.
(Round 2)
Who goes on the swing?
You go on the swing.
I...
Not bad.
(A bit impressive)
I skip the swing.
That's too easy.
(Overconfident)
Too easy?
I meant,
who are you sending?
You said it's easy. You go.
(No more being polite)
Naiwen.
You go.
Come on, Xingxu. Come on.
(Think I'm weak?)
I won't go easy on you.
Come on.
(Decisive Round)
Who goes on the swing?
You go on the swing.
I won't go on the swing.
I won't go.
(Spitting out inner thoughts)
I blurted out what I thought.
The Yes Man team wins.
You can freely choose to swap people.
What do you say?
Let's go over there.
(Seeking Yuning's opinion)
Yuning, do you want to jump?
I don't mind.
(Relaxed)
On the way here, he told me
he wants to jump.
(A bit embarrassing)
Okay, I'll jump.
Come on.
The worst that can happen is
coming back later.
(Leaving a way out)
Let's go take a look first, okay?
I have to see.
Right.
Okay.
Let's all get equipped first.
Cool.
Does it feel comfortable?
Okay.
Tighten this side a bit.
First time?
First time.
Let's go now.
Can't wait any longer.
Feeling very excited.
Onto the suspension bridge.
What's with the suspension bridge?
It's the kind that's suspending?
That's right.
We will cross
a 70-meter metal suspension bridge
to reach the swing platform.
Everyone, get ready to cross the bridge.
Let's go.
Let's go to the party.
Naiwen, once you get past
(Cheering on)
that first hurdle, you'll be great.
Naiwen,
as long as you can walk across,
you'll be the best.
Li Naiwen, you walk last.
- No.
- Walk in the middle of us.
I'll walk in the middle.
In the middle, he has no way to retreat.
If you walk in the middle,
you'll block us.
No, I won't.
No, we'll push him.
We'll push you.
(Go for it)
Let's go.
Go for it.
It feels like going into battle.
I'll protect you, Naiwen.
I'll protect you.
Okay.
It's very high.
It's shaking.
(Visible shaking)
It's okay.
(Groping)
(Looking straight ahead)
Easy.
As long as I don't look down.
Why did you stop?
(Easy for like a second)
Hello.
(The brave already own the world)
Who are you greeting?
There are people over there.
There are people.
It's so beautiful.
So thrilling.
Very beautiful.
This is a suspension bridge, Xingxu.
Suspension bridge effect.
Don't fall for me.
♪Don't fall for me♪
♪The stars in your eyes descending♪
Nai, is your heart moved?
Not moved.
Is your heart moved?
(Daring not to move anywhere)
Sorry.
What's wrong? You're so nervous?
I'm nervous. My heart is moved.
I'm so scared of this suspension bridge.
Xingxu, what should I do?
Are you nervous?
I'm nervous.
I've got you now.
I've got you.
Naiwen.
Not bad.
You're better than I imagined.
I'm not looking down.
Why is there a gap in the middle?
(Scared dizzy)
No, there isn't, Naiwen.
There isn't.
I'm so scared.
This really isn't scary.
Right?
(This one is also very scared)
It's very scary, alright?
When I look back at Ye,
she's like, "It's scary."
Don't ask. It's very scary.
It's suspended in mid-air.
Yes.
Wait a minute.
I realize that under my feet,
there's just one metal plate.
A very thin kind of metal plate.
Right.
(Belated fear)
I'm starting to regret this.
No.
It's over.
(No joke)
I'm really starting to regret this.
(Nothing else to say)
(Language system has failed)
I'm really starting to regret this.
Look at that.
I'm not looking.
(Thanks, but no)
I won't look for now.
You can't look down.
Looking down is unbearable.
Nai is so great.
Nai,
you did great.
Go take a look over there,
Naiwen.
Nai is so great.
(Holding tightly)
(140m high, 300m arc, up to 120km/h)
I'm starting to regret this.
(Scared)
This is really a bit scary.
(Excited)
Who goes first?
Us two...
Which of us goes first?
(Started?)
I...
I won't go down.
(Run quickly)
Zhou Ye goes first.
(Shut up)
Who?
Zhou Ye goes first.
She doesn't want to wait.
(Holding on tightly)
Can't wait.
I'll go first.
(Honglei goes first)
Go, Honglei.
You went first just now.
Yes, I went first just now.
Go for it, Honglei.
You can pick someone.
Or do you want to go alone?
Naiwen, you...
Are we going first?
No.
Do you want to go with me?
I want to go with you.
But I don't want to go first.
We'll go first.
(Not listening)
We...
(Are you even listening to me?)
(Instinct)
We're jumping anyway. Don't be afraid.
Naiwen,
you won't be scared if you don't look.
Don't look.
If you look,
you'll actually get more scared.
Really, it's fine.
(Don't look)
Wait a moment.
(Go for it, Nai)
Well,
the ones who are really scared
should jump first.
They have to jump first.
I'm okay. I think I'm okay.
(Courage arrived)
Suddenly I feel like I can do it again.
Let Nai and Honglei go first.
They will lead the way.
Okay?
Alright.
Then you two go first.
Is that okay,
Naiwen?
I don't know.
Let's stop talking.
Stop talking.
Let him decide for himself.
I'm feeling a bit dizzy now.
A bit dizzy.
Then who's going first with me?
The first leg?
I'll go with Honglei.
You're fierce.
You're amazing.
Thanks.
Lin Yi,
it's rare for me to think
you're better than me.
Thanks.
Go for it.
Go for it, Lin Yi.
Go, go, go.
Then later say that
I sing better than you.
(I didn't agree to that)
Open the door.
On your own?
Two people.
You two?
Together.
Okay.
Do you want to face that way?
For sitting down?
There are different ways here
for you to choose.
Back facing or front facing.
You can take a look
(Can choose the falling posture)
and see which way you'd like.
I think facing backward is a bit better.
It's easier to go down.
But you'll feel uncomfortable.
You won't see the view.
The main point is the rising view.
(Carefully selecting a viewing posture)
What posture is this?
That one?
(Good choice)
Yeah.
No, no, no.
That's too intimate.
- Forward?
- Just a normal one.
- Okay.
Yeah.
Okay.
There's wind.
That's normal, Naiwen.
It's normal to have wind.
How can there be no wind
at such a height?
Yes.
He's like,
"There's wind."
It's fine. Let them
go first.
You'll watch a round.
But after watching, you might...
Turn around and leave.
Let's go.
You're amazing.
- Okay?
- But who are you going with?
You've been assigned to me.
He needs to take him.
(Must be accompanied by young people)
He'll take him.
Then who else? Who else is jumping?
You two aren't jumping?
I'll stay here with him
to watch you guys.
Go for it.
Enjoy life to the fullest.
Or you can go with Nai.
I can go with Nai.
I'll take care of him.
(Weren't you...)
Is that okay?
If not, I'll take him. It's fine.
(50+ Naiwen waiting to be claimed)
I'm fine either way.
When I'm with him,
I have courage.
With others, I'm timid.
He's so timid.
It makes me brave.
That's just who I am.
You've still got it.
I'm telling you.
When you reach my age, you'll see.
Really.
When I was young, I wasn't...
I wasn't afraid of heights either.
When I was young, I was truly daring.
Top blowhard,
Fei.
Ultimate blowhard.
(Still the ultimate blowhard)
I'm the exact opposite, Fei.
When I was young,
I didn't dare do anything.
I didn't even dare
to ride a roller coaster.
I understand.
Because among all human traits,
only courage grows backward.
Everything else in a person
diminishes as we grow up,
except courage.
Are you ready?
Yeah, ready.
Come on over, guys.
Be brave.
Brave people enjoy the world first.
Come on.
Hurry.
I'll film him here.
I just have to hold onto this?
(Front row rock zone)
Once you're all set,
I'll take photos for you.
Just the two of them sitting there
looks scary to me.
No.
Even standing here, I'm scared.
It's fine.
Let's watch.
Won't you...
I'll sit with Nai.
(Back row chill zone)
You can sit and watch.
So scary.
Hi.
Hello.
Say hello.
New Zealand.
Look at me.
A game for the brave.
Okay.
Great.
Sit down?
Sit down. Yeah.
Sit down.
And put your feet out.
Okay.
Go for it, Honglei.
Great.
- Well done.
- Go for it.
You're the best.
The best.
Go for it.
Here we go.
(First group: Sun Honglei and Lin Yi,
pushed off the platform)
Here we go.
New Zealand.
I can't watch.
(Instinctively grabbing tightly)
My Queen, I'm here.
- My Queen,
- I'm here.
My Queen, I'm here.
Ready?
Yes!
Well done.
We're ready to go.
Three.
Two.
It's fine.
Three.
Two.
Wow The World!
The whole world is right here!
(Filmed by Chen Xingxu)
Here we go.
Wow The World!
The whole world is right here!
This is totally awesome.
Totally awesome.
(This is way beyond)
Wow The World!
This is too scary.
This is so intense.
This is super scary.
(Stuttering)
I can tell.
Super scary.
This is so thrilling.
(Already hooked)
It must be super thrilling.
It's fine now.
They are going up.
Just that one swing?
(Wanting more)
But that one was quite thrilling.
Quite thrilling.
The weightlessness was intense.
Are you okay?
Pretty scary.
Aren't you scared?
I'm not scared.
(Overcame)
(Pretend I didn't ask)
So thrilling. Who's going second?
Me.
(Conquering himself)
Come on. Who are you going with?
Nobody.
Come on, Fei.
- Want to come?
- No.
Are you going?
You go keep Yuning company.
Then I'll go with Yuning.
You look...
He's about to pass out.
(Offline)
It's fine. I'll save him later.
- Don't worry.
- Okay.
I'll take him.
(50+ Naiwen is claimed)
This is much scarier than that one.
This is terrifying.
I think it'll be...
Then my brain will just...
Then it'll just go blank.
And I won't scream anymore.
I'll just go numb.
(Blank)
Look at me.
Turn around.
He can't hear.
We're amazing, both of us.
(Self-affirmation)
We're amazing.
Look at me.
Turn around.
(Filmed by Chen Xingxu)
No problem at all.
Great job.
So awesome.
I'm really impressed.
Great job.
Now I feel a bit of excitement.
I didn't earlier.
You guys too.
When you hear me call,
just turn around.
Okay.
Yuning, do you have any song
you want to sing?
No.
Get me a bowl of instant noodles
to eat up there.
How was it?
How was it? Was it thrilling?
Thrilling.
So thrilling.
Once again?
Yeah.
One more round?
(So brave)
Again?
(The smile is gone)
(There's such a good thing?)
They're asking if you want to go again.
Press the button again.
No.
The first thing Honglei said to me was,
"That's it?
It's over?"
We prepared for a longer
rapid descent.
But I didn't expect it to be so short.
Didn't get enough.
(Indeed left wanting more)
It was a bit short indeed.
Bye-bye.
Cool.
Then I'll lead Naiwen for another jump.
(Completely in love)
Sure.
Naiwen, I'll lead you.
I'll sit for a while.
What's up? Why are you crying?
(Scared to tears?)
Cried?
No.
He's moved.
I'm rubbing my eyes.
Not to the point of crying.
Like the wind got in my eyes.
(I'm not crying; my eyelashes are drowning)
So beautiful.
(So scary)
(Emergency monitoring of vital signs)
(Everything is normal so far)
Staring at this is pointless.
He's super anxious.
It's pointless to watch this.
It's fine, Naiwen.
I'll jump with you.
If you don't want to jump,
that's fine too.
No need to force yourself.
(Acquired acrophobia,
ongoing psychological adjustment)
Okay.
Okay. Nothing in your pockets?
Nothing.
Want forwards?
Yeah.
Don't you want to try
something different?
Backwards?
No.
So awesome.
Let me check
the two of them.
Okay. Ready?
Ready.
You're okay. I know you're not scared.
(Not the same me from 10 minutes ago)
I'm not scared at all.
- Really?
- Not scared at all.
Even I'm a bit scared.
I think this is very thrilling.
It's fine. Really fine.
(Really?)
Come on.
Let's go.
We need to stand on the line.
Very high.
I'm not scared at all.
Not scared at all.
(Trembling voice, frantic hands)
It's okay.
Okay.
That's okay.
Take this off.
This is gone.
Thanks.
I'm not scared at all.
Not scared at all.
Look at me.
(As if I dare look)
Sit down.
Look.
Can I sit down?
(Can't sit down)
Sit down.
(Indeed, it's very scary.)
No, wait.
I'm not scared at all.
Not scared at all.
Go for it, Yuning.
Go for it, Yuwen.
Go for it.
Great job. Super awesome.
Go for it. You're the best.
(Second group: Liu Yuning, Wang Yuwen
Pushed off the platform)
Yuning, don't look down.
Okay, I won't.
Look ahead.
Yes, look ahead.
Cheer each other on.
Go for it, Yuning.
Okay.
This scene
is truly beautiful.
Three.
Two.
One.
The brave
enjoys the world first.
(Filmed by Chen Xingxu)
It's fine now.
Right. Once you reach this point,
you don't feel scared anymore.
It's just comfortable.
Comfortable.
That's it?
That's it.
Are you okay?
How was it?
Okay. It's alright.
Only
two seconds of weightlessness.
Right.
But it's very thrilling.
Okay.
Let's face the camera
and say, "That's it?"
That's...
Three, two, one.
That's it?
(Official photographer appears on time)
Turn around.
(Filmed by Chen Xingxu)
Look at me.
Great job.
Well done.
Okay.
Let's go, Naiwen.
Let them come up first.
(Don't be afraid)
Awesome. Truly awesome.
Wonderful, Yuning.
So impressive.
Yuning.
Yuning, Yuning.
Can't do it without you.
That's it?
Mastered it.
Need to put on airs.
Yuning,
let me know
your real feelings.
All your fear lasts only two seconds.
Right.
I think it's less than two seconds.
A bit over one second.
Really.
Once it reaches that point,
that feeling...
Right.
Is all gone.
All your fear lasts only two seconds.
I think it's less than two seconds.
A bit over one second.
It's okay.
If you...
Go.
Okay.
(Went all out)
Let me tell you,
you definitely won't regret it.
You definitely won't regret it.
But you will definitely be scared.
But you won't regret it.
Nai is amazing.
He can do it.
He definitely can do it.
Are you okay?
(Good)
So-so.
(But)
Which way are you choosing?
(Choose the falling method)
The normal way.
Just sitting.
(Guess you like it)
No.
Stand on that line.
Yes.
Give me your hand.
Right.
So intense.
Nai, a real man.
Don't hold onto it.
Naiwen, don't look down. Look ahead.
Naiwen.
(Slowly moving)
(Holding tightly)
You can do it.
Just minutes.
Sorry.
No problem.
(Trying to sit on the swing)
Wait a moment.
My heart is racing.
I understand how Naiwen feels.
I was just like that a moment ago.
Okay. Lower him down.
Lower him down.
Right, Naiwen.
Wait.
This isn't necessary.
Completely unnecessary.
Sorry.
You're not going, right?
Right. I'm not going for now.
Open it.
(Li Naiwen interrupts the challenge)
Are you sure you don't want to try?
No. He doesn't want to.
Okay.
Forget it, Naiwen.
Just quit.
Naiwen, I understand you.
Great job.
Naiwen, don't stand here.
Go to that shady spot.
You indeed have
a physiological fear of heights.
Physiological.
Xingxu, shall I jump with you?
I can accompany you.
Then let's do it.
Okay.
Do it again.
Really impressive.
Well done, Yuwen.
Wang Yuwen is so awesome.
She
is not scared.
This scene is so beautiful.
(Third group: Chen Xingxu, Wang Yuwen
Pushed out the platform) Go for it.
Go for it, Xingxu.
Come on, say something.
The brave enjoys the world repeatedly.
Three.
Two.
One.
His hair is standing on end.
So impressive.
Let's lie down.
This is the core.
So thrilling.
Why is it so thrilling?
Hello.
Wave your hand.
This is really well shot.
This is so romantic.
They should use this
for drama promotion.
Break ten thousand
in one day, I tell you.
White shirt and suit.
Well done.
Later, you can watch
the whole process.
Okay.
You shot it very well.
Still hesitating.
You won't regret this.
But you'll definitely be scared.
I'm scared at that point.
My body just made me...
You even felt nauseous.
Just now,
I felt nauseous too.
My breathing was tight just now.
Already had difficulty breathing.
Only saying it now.
Not filmed, right?
Delete it.
Only keep the "that's it" part.
Right. Go directly
to "that's it".
I'll go with you again.
Won't let you be alone.
Xingxu can go with you one more time.
No. I can't.
Let's go.
Alright. Then let's go.
- No hesitation.
- No regrets.
Let's go.
Then no more hesitation.
Alright.
But we are self-disciplined.
(Just endure not sitting)
Okay.
You lead.
I'll lead?
Okay.
Can you do it?
I can.
Walking down this suspension bridge
isn't easy,
Naiwen.
I know.
Slow down.
It's swaying a lot.
I'm getting a bit scared.
♪Swaying and shaking♪
Yuning is going to fall in love with me.
What?
Because of the suspension bridge effect.
Everyone on this bridge has
fallen in love with each other.
This whole row is in love.
All in love.
Falling in love.
Fallen in love with each other.
Does your heart race?
Are you in love?
Coming to catch you.
♪The world is so interesting♪
It was worthwhile. Okay.
It was worthwhile.
I'm the leader.
I'm back with a bunch of brave people.
Okay. Already very impressive.
Standing there at that moment
is the scariest.
Just standing there is very impressive.
So cool.
Feels like returning
from a victorious battle.
It feels like I jumped myself.
(Courage lies not in being flawless, but in the resolve to walk on the platform)
Today I could eat a horse.
It was still quite thrilling.
I'll pretend
I jumped.
Yuning is impressive.
He overcame fear.
Now it's time for a hearty meal.
Let's go.
Why do I feel like riding this car
is scarier than that bungee?
Actually, just now,
when crossing that bridge
and standing there,
I felt my brain
had already restarted.
So beautiful.
A small stream.
♪The road is always too narrow♪
Now everyone is here.
Some jumped twice,
some jumped once,
and some didn't even want to jump.
(Me making excuses to save face)
Some wanted to but finally gave up.
I think for me,
the biggest gain this time
is that I overcame my curiosity.
(There's still a master)
I can control myself.
I think I'm so mature.
"Top blowhard."
When I was sitting up there, I already
had a racing heart.
Already couldn't catch my breath.
I understood.
I can get it.
I can understand.
You couldn't hear
what we were saying anymore.
Actually...
Yeah.
When you're not talking, it's very...
Awkward.
No, very,
very peaceful.
When you don't speak,
you can hear the sound of the mountains.
The sound of wind and water
in the mountains.
You can hear your echo.
Yes.
Totally worth experiencing.
It truly is worth experiencing.
The scenery is different.
Peaceful years.
Really beautiful.
Like a fairy tale town.
So nice.
I feel like it's going to take me
a long time to withdraw from this.
Yeah.
Even more looking forward
to our next recording together.
(The moment our hearts beat as one
side by side, the lingering feeling hits hard)
(Arriving at the restaurant.)
Let's go.
Come on, everyone.
I love tonight's dishes.
Here we truly have scampi freedom.
Tonight's chef is called
Yu Yashan.
She is a Chinese female head chef.
She is the winner of New Zealand's 2025
"Taste of Art" annual champion.
Let's first thank the chef.
Okay.
Alright.
Thank you.
So young.
Thank you for providing us
with such delicious food.
It was really delicious.
Where are you from?
I'm from Qingdao.
(Yu Yashan, 2025 New Zealand
'Taste of Art' Annual Grand Champion)
From Qingdao.
So you make great seafood dishes.
Yes.
No wonder you make great seafood dishes.
Awesome.
Today's selection
is all local New Zealand ingredients.
From appetizers to main courses,
everything is from around Queenstown,
especially
the South Island.
The ingredients are excellent.
Really, really impressive.
Thank you.
Thank you, chef.
Thank this...
Thank you.
Beautiful lady.
This salmon...
Jeez.
This salmon is absolutely amazing.
It smells so good.
Just by smelling this sauce,
you can tell it's delicious.
It's blowing my mind.
This lamb is really tasty.
Its
temperature is also top-notch.
This lamb is indeed
living up to its reputation.
Delicious.
Is that tartare good?
That venison tartare.
(Venison tartare)
You should try it.
(Served raw)
Go get it.
I don't dare try it.
Forget it.
Raw venison, right?
A bit unsure.
It's fine.
Then I have to try one.
Cheers.
How is it?
Does it have a bit of venison flavor?
This venison tartare is so delicious!
Put it over there.
It's so delicious!
Really, Honglei?
It's exceptionally good.
Let me describe it to you.
Does your family make dumplings
for Chinese New Year?
Of course.
Dumplings with chive and egg filling.
The filling.
Before wrapping.
It tastes just like eating
that filling raw.
Like you forgot to cook it.
(Interesting)
It's like the chive and egg filling
just mixed.
(Now I'm curious)
Just mixing in the soy sauce
and stuff
before it's even wrapped.
Your description actually sparked his...
(Aroused curiosity)
(Another bro can't hold back any longer)
What you said
actually made them...
They originally didn't want to eat it.
This meat is gamey.
I disagree.
What do you think?
You disagree?
You still think it's a delicacy, right?
I think it tastes
like the bottom of a burger,
that bottom layer,
mayonnaise or something.
Some sauce flavor.
Your description is even worse than his.
But I think it's okay.
It's actually pretty good.
It's quite tasty.
(No one beats you two)
Alright, I'm stuffed.
I'm overwhelmed by the aroma.
I'm full.
Our New Zealand trip
is about to end soon.
At the end,
everywhere we go,
we always
leave some memories behind.
Everyone.
Artist.
How come after jumping once,
your English improved so much?
(Can't deny it)
Seems so.
It's like a light bulb went off.
You've been speaking English non-stop.
Well,
these two days my confidence
just shot up.
Because he kept talking to me,
explaining the meaning,
asking how it was,
and how I felt.
And I actually understood.
She asked me,
"Is this your first time doing this?"
I said, "Yes, the first time."
She asked if I was scared.
I said I wasn't scared.
I've achieved soul-level communication.
No.
From the moment
they started strapping you in,
you understood everything they said.
Understood everything.
Like "sit down" and "how's the buckle",
understood it all.
It just clicked.
She asked if anything was in my pockets.
I said
nothing.
Look.
She asked, "Are your pockets empty?"
Empty.
We're a bit alike.
That's right.
I experienced "astral projection".
You got "English possessed".
Alright.
"English possession".
Both have
a very strong survival instinct.
Yes.
I'm telling you, it's possible
that after you jump,
both you and Zhou Ye
can sing better.
But when I was bungee jumping,
I tried to sing.
And then?
It was completely off-key.
And the sound quality
was totally wrecked.
(Definitely not this level)
Our last mission in New Zealand.
Our last mission in New Zealand
is an a cappella showdown.
We'll form
two independent a cappella vocal groups.
Team members may be
assigned different voice parts
based on their vocal ranges
and strengths,
performing the songs
in unaccompanied harmony.
After practice,
both teams
will take the stage to perform.
A cappella.
What are you laughing at?
Well.
If we sing normally in one key,
it will definitely be a cappella,
because no one is in the same key.
Let me tell you, that's not true.
Actually, a cappella makes it
easier to...
Right.
Take shape.
Why?
Easier.
For example, he is just...
(Searching for words)
Just that.
(Sparkling)
His pitch is a little shaky,
so he can focus on B-BOX
and laying down
the drum beats instead, right?
(Do you mean B-BOX?)
(Suddenly spreading
from person to another)
Shout-singing.
(Secretly working hard)
Then let's group by seats.
(Team A: Chen Xingxu, Lin Yi,
Wang Yuwen, Liu Yuning)
(Team B: Sun Honglei, Li Naiwen,
Guo Jingfei, Zhou Ye)
The four of us?
The four of us, yes.
We're definitely winning.
(Confident)
I like their mysterious confidence.
Then you're doomed.
(Demonstrating bottom line)
It's this B-Box.
(Rhythm part)
This is the double bass.
Okay.
(Bass part, but not too low version)
This is the singer.
No.
I'm the erhu.
You're an electronic erhu.
It has a bit of a cyberpunk feel.
So,
let's use our work
to give everyone a little surprise.
Alright.
Once that's said,
I got goosebumps all over.
Even more so than bungee jumping.
(A little musical Easter egg
for the Southern Hemisphere)
Come on, let's listen to it.
I can't do this. I can't.
I can imagine it.
This thing will definitely
be hilarious when we perform.
Then what are we doing?
(Soul-searching question)
We have to make all the sounds you hear.
Four people make this sound.
(Yes, you heard it right)
We can do it.
We can.
No.
I don't know how to do this beat.
Who cares if it's right or not?
(One dares to persuade)
Just do it.
Then I can do it.
(One dares to listen)
Just get the rhythm out.
Right?
(Watch what confidence is)
(Who made him happy again?)
(Pfft, doo, doo)
(Too noisy)
Oh, no.
Very childlike.
Four people have to create this effect?
Right.
(The situation is grim)
Do we want it to be a mess
or particularly refined?
Can...
can we be refined?
If you want it particularly refined,
give us a year.
(A year to perfect one song)
Three years.
Do you know how I spent
those three years?
Refined.
I think being refined is fine.
Give us...
Twenty minutes.
(Ning's confidence)
Really, Yuning?
That much room
for adjustment?
That's right.
I like their mysterious confidence.
Before we start practicing,
let's toast with some lemon chewing.
Here's to everyone's creative success!
Cheers, artists!
Artists.
For New Zealand.
Hope you like it.
Here are the professional props.
Do you have to memorize all the "doo"?
No.
You don't need to memorize any of that.
Actually,
people like us,
the professionals
who play instruments,
we just remember it within the beat.
We are playing with music.
Play.
Play with it.
Just follow the music from the start,
and improvise.
Right, we master it.
Alright, I'll sit over there.
We're a team.
We have a professional vocal coach.
(Yuning's professional stage,
come if you have a dream)
We're doing the same song, right?
Right.
(Hopeless)
Can four people
pull this off?
How does that relate to the lyrics?
Because we have to sing.
(Doesn't look like he understands)
(Observing the opponent)
Let's divide it first.
(Step 1: Divide the lyrics)
Play the beginning.
(Secretly learning)
Can we listen to it again?
(Trying to hold the family together)
Those intro parts are needed.
(Ye the Lark, one helping three)
(Splitting lyrics in progress)
♪A million reasons, all full of holes♪
♪Hurry, speak.
Once spoken, it's most bare♪
Just leave the singing to Ye.
Can you sing?
(Is it okay?)
♪Even if we die♪
♪We must love♪
♪The tenderness of a kiss♪
Alright.
Okay.
Then we two do the harmony.
For the beginning,
let's enrich it with some instruments.
I think...
I'll sing this alone.
♪It's about the result♪
Everyone sing together then.
Just come together at the end.
Right.
Then the front part is...
This part in the beginning,
bro, you take it.
Okay.
This one.
The first one is yours.
Also...
Wait, let me write it down.
Honglei, this one.
I can do the very beginning.
We've already divided the instruments.
This front part is Honglei's.
Which one?
Honglei does that one.
Then "make it" is yours.
Listen, first Honglei.
Honglei.
Fei comes in.
I come in with this.
No.
Who gets "Guo Degang"?
(How did Guo Degang get here?)
Listen.
Guo Degang...
See, isn't it "Guo Degang"?
I think him alone isn't enough.
I'll back you up.
Come on.
Let's do this together.
That's like Native American.
(Mainly about momentum)
Hurry up.
Come on, join in.
(Ye's class)
- Woof, woof...
- Meow, meow...
Look how professional they are.
(Yuning's professional lesson)
First, the underlying logic.
Okay.
Ignore the singing for now.
First, there's a DJ scratching sound.
Can you do this?
(Appreciating)
Good.
(A natural-born beatboxer)
Absolutely crushing it.
(Arranging one by one)
Then, for you,
there's a siren in it.
Let me hear it.
Just shout your name, Wen.
(Teaching according to the student)
Wen
Okay.
Your part
goes like this.
You go like this.
Like this.
♪Wen♪
Formula 1 car.
Keep
- making the sound.
- Okay.
Okay.
The fourth one comes in.
The kick drum starts.
What's a kick drum?
It's just you.
(After teaching him, we teach you)
Okay.
His bass is pretty good.
This is art.
Art.
Wait.
Let me hear it.
Don't listen to him.
Ignore him.
(I will come on my own)
You'll be exhausted doing this.
(So what?)
I was just assigned to that group.
Actually, I'd be helpful in this group.
See, at the critical moment...
(Missing a bird-teasing old man?)
Okay, let's go with this.
Come on.
We're ready.
Ready.
Come on.
(The first a cappella PK battle
Sun Honglei, Li Naiwen, Guo Jingfei, Zhou Ye)
Come on.
Let's go!
Hello everyone,
we are a group
from Beijing.
We'll present a song for you,
- Exuberant.
Music Director,
Zhou Ye.
(Laughing very happily)
(Music Director: Zhou Ye the Lark)
(Secretly upgrading the title)
Stage effects,
Li Naiwen.
(Li Naiwen, especially funny,
also counts as effects)
Stage Director, Sun Honglei.
(Sun Honglei,
an actor, director and manager)
Sound Director, Guo Jingfei.
(Guo Jingfei,
always monitoring bird sounds)
My friends,
our honor rest on this battle.
The show now begins.
It's like a drama.
Okay.
Come on, bow.
I'll be here.
Bowing to the audience.
(Exuberant, by Sun Honglei, Li Naiwen,
Guo Jingfei, Zhou Ye)
(Show Time)
First, set the beat,
♪Five, six, seven, eight♪
♪We'll make it♪
Zhou Ye, good!
Not bad.
This mic is a bit dirty.
(What a mistake)
We should have sung first.
This mic isn't working well now.
It feels like a karaoke room.
Karaoke room.
(Laughing to tears)
♪It's about the result♪
(Started late, giving it all)
♪Result♪
(Apologizing to the audience)
(Please accept these memes)
Encore!
Not bad.
If there are
fans of Guo Degang,
(Sorry for the offense)
please forgive us.
Battle.
Come on.
(Liu Yuning, Chen Xingxu,
Wang Yuwen, Lin Yi)
Hello everyone, we are
- Jurassic Park.
Three T-Rexes and one zookeeper.
Okay.
(The keeper and T-Rexes)
Alright.
I am
the singer and bassist.
(Liu Yuning, Vocal and Bass,
the only professional singer)
I am the lead female vocalist,
and also the visual.
(Vocal and Visual, Wang Yuwen,
beautiful and sweet-voiced)
I am the kick drum.
Kick drum.
(Drummer Chen Xingxu, Rhythm Master)
Drummer Chen Xingxu.
I am the synthesizer.
The synthesizer!
(Synthesizer: Lin Yi,
sound sculptor, sound wave magician)
See, they came up so confidently.
We'll bring you a song,
a pure a cappella song,
Exuberant.
For everyone.
Everyone, scream for us.
But don't scream too long,
it's easy to get hypoxia.
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome!
DJ, Wen.
MC, Xingxu.
The excitement is about to begin.
Welcome to our party.
Let's go.
(Exuberant, by Liu Yuning, Chen Xingxu,
Wang Yuwen, Lin Yi)
(Showtime)
(Xingxu in)
♪We'll make it♪
♪The rights and wrongs are too many♪
♪Arriving at an exuberant occasion♪
♪Mixing his impulse and her loneliness♪
♪Regardless of the consequences♪
♪You say♪
♪I want results♪
♪Turn around and do it again♪
♪Men, women, don't wait any longer♪
♪Freedom, freedom, we want freedom now♪
Thank you.
This synthesizer
is amazing.
So hardcore.
Your synthesizer is fantastic.
Their synthesizer is the latest version.
Upgraded.
Ours is not as good.
By your synthesizer, do you mean
that "Guo Degang" thing?
Yes.
This is the best five hundred yuan
I've ever spent.
I spent five hundred yuan in Beijing
for two classes.
This is the best money I've ever spent
in my entire life.
So, there's a saying.
In life,
nothing you learn is ever wasted.
(Every step counts)
Really, you can use it.
Exactly.
You are the king here.
With five hundred yuan,
you became a king.
This New Zealand trip
is very fulfilled.
Very happy.
So happy.
(I'm very happy to come to New Zealand.)
(The last time I saw everyone)
(was at the All Star Night.)
(I didn't expect that now I truly)
(am sitting here with everyone.)
I was very nervous when I first came.
And you three,
whom I always know about
but never familiar with...
Just three shameless rascals.
(Please don't sink together)
But unexpectedly,
I'm always on the same team with you.
I'm so happy.
And we always won.
Yeah.
As long as I'm with you,
we'll definitely win.
I'm your lucky star.
Oh, that was it.
We're riding on your luck.
Yeah.
And today,
during that bungee jump,
I was actually very scared.
I only had 30% courage to jump,
the rest of me was scared.
But I saw everyone around
cheering me on,
including
Lin Yi and Yuwen.
Everyone cheering me on.
I was really touched.
You gave me courage
to jump.
In short, thank you all very much.
I'm very happy, thank you.
Ye, will you come again next time?
Yes.
Okay.
I'm their lucky star.
What if I leave
and they never win again?
That makes sense.
I want to thank the production team.
I haven't traveled for a long time.
And I found
that I began to
lose interest in traveling.
Through this work opportunity,
I got to go abroad again.
What impressed me most
was
Rotorua's
Springs.
The water was so clear.
You could see the bottom.
The nature was very well protected.
Everyone took back their trash.
It's like, whatever you give to nature,
it will give back to you.
This is what I hope for.
We humans must get better and better.
We must protect nature more and more.
Last year,
when this show was on,
my daughter hadn't turned eight yet.
All her classmates were watching it.
When I went to her classmates' homes,
I was especially popular.
So popular.
They grabbed me and asked,
"How tall is Liu Yuning really?"
Take me next time, bro.
Next time, I have to bring Yuning.
He will boost my status.
Otherwise, I wouldn't even dare
to visit the kids' classmates.
Just kidding.
Before coming, I didn't look up
about what's fun to do.
But we did everything we should.
Seeing those beautiful views,
I felt very happy.
After working for many years,
or so-called
having experienced some things,
you seem to prefer these kinds of
places that calm you down,
where you can see the animals.
No.
"No"? You think you're training a dog?
(Those sheep were grazing there.)
(You could just watch them)
(all day.)
(I didn't have that feeling before.)
(I used to be very restless.)
(I just wanted to run,)
(pursue a better tomorrow.)
(But now when I see these things,)
(I really yearn for this kind of life.)
During the Chinese New Year period,
in the first month of our Chinese year,
being with a group of good friends,
coming to a place to have fun,
sharing,
seeing beautiful scenery,
and playing exciting things,
it makes me very happy.
Especially this time,
we have
Fei,
Lin Yi,
and Ye,
who newly joined our Earth Group.
I mean,
at the beginning, I was a bit nervous,
wondering if everyone
would need a breaking-in period.
But just in one day,
I felt we are the same kind of people.
And I was very happy.
Thank you, everyone.
Of course, first we must welcome Lin Yi,
Jingfei
and Ye.
The addition of the three of them
not only infused fresh blood,
but also brought more possibilities.
Together,
we also tasted New Zealand cuisine.
Quickly, take a picture.
Take a photo.
The beef is delicious.
It's actually like hot pot.
This is very interesting.
This is really a great experience.
I was quite impressed by the rafting.
It was safer than I imagined,
but also more thrilling.
Because at the time...
Do you know why?
We thought we would fly.
All the way down,
sitting
on the kayak.
And then
the coach
asked if we want to swim down.
(Li Naiwen)
When we went down,
it was so thrilling!
I can feel that
we are now
getting closer
and closer.
This is family.
This time and my last time
are a little different.
Last time,
our last season
happened to be in a period
right after I finished filming.
I wasn't very familiar with everyone.
I went from wrapping a project
to joining
this team.
I was actually a bit dazed at that time.
But this time,
it feels like coming home.
I feel like I need work,
but I need everyone's company even more.
This way, I won't fall
back into my own
so-called introverted
or strange little circle.
These ten days have taken me from
a state of slowly
becoming monotonous again
to opening up a bit more,
thanks to you guys.
With this attitude,
I will embrace the life ahead,
until I see everyone again.
This time, we really experienced a lot,
unique and special extreme sports
in New Zealand.
Before,
when I was relatively young,
I was someone who didn't dare
to ride even roller coasters.
I feel that with you guys,
I get this certain power.
I hope
with your encouragement,
and in such
an environment,
I can experience my first times.
Even if it might be the only time,
it's worth it.
Today's bungee jumping
and
yesterday's paragliding
are my first experiences.
Before I stood on that platform,
I didn't know I would have the courage
to jump.
Because everyone from the Earth Group
was there,
I felt especially safe.
I knew they would encourage me,
cheer for me,
and celebrate with me.
Every day we spent together
was full of amazing opportunities.
You want to take us, right?
Okay.
So,
you don't busy?
We can take you there.
(Actually, sometimes encounters
are very meaningful.)
(So I think,)
(this reunion)
(gives meaning to the encounter.)
And the Earth Group makes me
look forward to waking up every day
and reluctant to fall asleep.
But when I woke up this morning,
I did feel a bit empty.
Because I'm counting down again.
I thought,
oh no, it's the last day again.
Then I told Lin Yi,
"No.
I'm going to have withdrawal symptoms."
Lin Yi said,
"Then the next thing is to look forward
to our next meeting."
So I think,
starting from now,
I'm going to start looking forward
to the next trip.
When I first came to New Zealand,
I was...
I was very nervous even before coming.
Actually,
I had already met most
of the Earth Group.
But last time,
we met
in the air.
Today, we met on the ground.
Right, on the ground.
But I'm very happy.
There weren't the things I imagined,
like being
very anxious and uneasy.
I feel that in these ten days,
I have grown a lot.
This is something I didn't expect.
And this is
my first time in New Zealand.
I experienced so many firsts.
My first time
soaking in a volcanic hot spring,
(volcanic mud,)
(first time watching a Maori war dance,)
(and first time riding a swing.)
Wow The World!
The whole world is right here!
These are all very unforgettable.
Last time I came, I said,
I had severe withdrawal symptoms.
Now I feel like I'm already starting.
Yes.
I think it's mainly because
everyone is here.
(When you come with friends and family,)
(you feel like,)
(this beautiful scenery becomes)
(more tangible and vivid.)
- Wow The World.
- The whole world is right here.
(The end is also a new beginning.
Let's look forward to the next journey)
(Next Episode Preview)
This stop,
the Earth Group will experience
romantic Paris with their partners.
My partner knows it's me,
or maybe doesn't.
Partner, I'm coming right away.
Don't make me guess.
I'm telling you,
my sixth sense is very accurate.
I wish it's...
Honglei, I guess.
Lin Yi.
Wen.
The three of us,
when we're together,
we just eat and drink.
I don't know if it's romantic or not,
but anyway,
it's a bit wasteful.
I see our boat.
I always thought this tower was black.
It's so beautiful.
It's so magnificent.
Whisper Word Guessing.
One person wears headphones
and describes the word,
the other person guesses the word.
No, he runs too fast.
Who is it?
Right under my nose.
He kept saying
the same sentence.
If I make it too detailed,
I'm afraid they'll guess it.
The next game
has a little bit to do with acting.
It involves professional stuff again.
You can perform a musical.
♪So that's how it is♪
What are you talking about?
What are you saying?
He didn't understand.
Simply put,
I said it for nothing.
Alright,
stop talking about
those advantages of yours.
Wrong.
Can't you say this?
Let's break up.
How many times have I told you
we have a family feud?
She is the woman I love most.
Actually,
his brother was my first love.
Song Qian, have you gone crazy?
My lady,
why, from the moment you entered,
has your smile never faded?
I'm naturally a smiley person.
Well,
that was new to me.
(Earth Group's situational deduction,
please look forward to it.)
Go.
Let's go.
Let's go chase the "blue tears".
Look, the stars are all lit up now,
how beautiful.
Under the moonlight,
rowing boats, quite romantic.
Yes.
Don't you feel it's a magical experience
being on the sea late at night?
I think I see it.
Yes.
It's so obvious.
(Earth Group's Blue Tears journey,
please look forward to it.)
(Wow The World, show schedule)
(Post-credits scene)
♪The world is so interesting♪
Come on, let's take a selfie together.
Come on, selfie.
Three,
two,
one.
So precisely timed?
Even sneezing
has to be this precisely timed?
Come on.